const Q1A = [
"<span class='ans'>0.55</span>",
"1.1",
"1.52",
"0.98"
]
const Q2A = [
"<span class='ans'>the back should be straight and knees bent, to use your leg muscles</span>",
"bend at the back and keep legs straight",
"use your back muscles as they are the strongest",
"feet together with toes spread and lift slowly, using your back muscles"
]
const Q3A = [
"<span class='ans'>schematic diabgram</span>",
"wiring diagram",
"plan layout",
"none of these options"
]
const Q4A = [
"<span class='ans'>The Ontario Ministry of Consumer Services</span>",
"The Department of National Defence",
"The Ontario Board of Labour",
"The Office of the Premier"
]
const Q5A = [
"<span class='ans'>immediately shut off the supply of gas to the appliance or work; promptly give oral notice of the shutting off of the gas to the distributor; promptly give written notice to the user, (i) describing the condition that constitutes the immediate hazard, and (ii) directing that the appliance or work not be used until the condition is corrected</span>",
"affix a notice containing the information required in clause to the appliance or work",
"within 14 days of finding the condition, give written notice of the condition to the distributor, including notice that the supply of gas has been shut off.",
"all of these options"
]
const Q6A = [
"<span class='ans'>that your work will reflect the same care and consideration</span>",
"that you are on the fast track to success",
"that you enjoy reading fashion magazines",
"are more concerned with appearances than performance"
]
const Q7A = [
"<span class='ans'>responsibilities are identified in the local act, regulations and bulletins</span>",
"unsafe situations must always be reported to CSA",
"a gas technician is required to notify the manufacturer",
"a gas technician is required to obtain direction from his or her direct supervisor"
]
const Q8A = [
"when the flashback arresters removed",
"to sample liquid fuel",
"for sampling gas vapours not identified as suitable by the manufacturer",
"<span class='ans'>all of these options</span>"
]
const Q9A = [
"m (meters)",
"<span class='ans'>m 2 (meters squared)</span>",
"m 3 (meters cubic)",
"none of these options"
]
const Q10A = [
"wiring",
"drain and vent lines",
"future lines",
"<span class='ans'>hidden lines</span>"
]
const Q11A = [
"<span class='ans'>to perform a follow-up to ensue the customer is still satisfied</span>",
"to try to sell the customer additional products and services",
"to sell the customers contact information to other companies who have products and services for sale",
"all of these options"
]
const Q12A = [
"<span class='ans'>0.51</span>",
"144",
"1.53",
"0.55"
]
const Q13A = [
"<span class='ans'>all of these options</span>",
"local zoning requirements",
"the building code",
"local fire regulations"
]
const Q14A = [
"<span class='ans'>a calm sincere concern and interest in facial expressions</span>",
"avoid eye contact and whistle a happy tune",
"an intimidating posture",
"crossed arms and a sly smile"
]
const Q15A = [
"<span class='ans'>I can understand why you feel that way</span>",
"I feel you, brother",
"don't worry, many people have had worse problems",
"it won't seem so bad once you get our bill"
]
const Q16A = [
"<span class='ans'>a quick opening die</span>",
"a tie dye",
"a ratcheting die",
"a solid die"
]
const Q17A = [
"<span class='ans'>the tube type and the liquid type</span>",
"the tube type and the pocket type",
"the liquid type and the pocket type",
"the pocket type and the dye type"
]
const Q18A = [
"<span class='ans'>CSA B149.2-10</span>",
"CSA B149.1-10",
"CSA B149.3-10",
"CSA B51-09"
]
const Q19A = [
"hire an interpreter",
"recommend the customer rake additional language training",
"<span class='ans'>ask the customer to write their request</span>",
"ask the customer to find someone who speaks better English"
]
const Q20A = [
"use a steady, raised and confident voice",
"stare at the customer with a look of disgust when they are speaking",
"<span class='ans'>always avoid conflict and arguments with customers</span>",
"call your supervisor and let the customer argue with them"
]
const Q21A = [
"1/2 inch",
"2 inch",
"2 1/2 inch",
"<span class='ans'>3 inches</span>"
]
const Q22A = [
"actions that are taken quickly and effectively",
"any action that does not endanger personal property",
"<span class='ans'>actions that are reasonable in the circumstances and would be conducted by any reasonable person</span>",
"any action that can save a life"
]
const Q23A = [
"American National Standard Institute",
"Canadian Standards Association",
"International Organization for Standardization",
"<span class='ans'>all of these options</span>"
]
const Q24A = [
"2 inch",
"<span class='ans'>a minimum 3 inch diameter</span>",
"a minimum 1/4 inch NPT",
"2 1/2 inch"
]
const Q25A = [
"using an exhaust fan",
"<span class='ans'>open doors and windows</span>",
"using the fan on the furnace",
"using an open flange"
]
const Q26A = [
"<span class='ans'>18 inches</span>",
"12 inches",
"10 inches",
"36 inches"
]
const Q27A = [
"fall protection",
"respirator",
"<span class='ans'>eye protection</span>",
"hearing protection"
]
const Q28A = [
"the Fuel Safety Act",
"<span class='ans'>the Technical Standards and Safety Act</span>",
"the Technical Fuel and Pressure Safety Act",
"the Mandatory Fuel Standards Act"
]
const Q29A = [
"<span class='ans'>a carbide-tipped blade</span>",
"an abrasive blade",
"a steel-toothed blade",
"all of these options"
]
const Q30A = [
"<span class='ans'>CSA</span>",
"TSSA",
"CGA",
"AGA"
]
const Q31A = [
"<span class='ans'>employer or supervisor</span>",
"local law enforcement official",
"TSSA",
"Canadian Standard Association"
]
const Q32A = [
"a product index",
"a list of materials",
"<span class='ans'>specifications</span>",
"none of these options"
]
const Q33A = [
"a two wheel cover",
"<span class='ans'>three wheel cutter</span>",
"a one wheel cutter",
"a no wheel cutter"
]
const Q34A = [
"Confirm their request is possible but that it will cost considerably more money",
"tell them that their request is not possible and they should leave these decisions to the experts",
"<span class='ans'>calmly and patiently identify what you are able to do and not what you are unable to do</span>",
"firmly restate what you are able to do and offer them that if they are not happy they can hire another company"
]
const Q35A = [
"general",
"<span class='ans'>pipe</span>",
"electrical",
"all of these options"
]
const Q36A = [
"CSA B149.1 gas code",
"<span class='ans'>the manufacturers product specifications</span>",
"product sales brochure",
"none of these options"
]
const Q37A = [
"10 X",
"<span class='ans'>100 X</span>",
"1000 X",
"50 X"
]
const Q38A = [
"Clause 11 of the B149.2-10 and the national building code",
"<span class='ans'>Clause 11 of the B149.2-10and the CSA Z240.1</span>",
"Clause 11 of the B149.2-10 and the CSA Z240.2",
"Clause 11 of the B149.2-10 and the national fire code"
]
const Q39A = [
"communication",
"<span class='ans'>workplace behavior</span>",
"appearance",
"attitude"
]
const Q40A = [
"the duties of employers and other persons are always described in section 3",
"provincial occupational health and safety act do not identify employer responsibilities",
"<span class='ans'>this will vary from province to province</span>",
"none of these options"
]
const Q41A = [
"red",
"<span class='ans'>green</span>",
"blue",
"yellow"
]
const Q42A = [
"<span class='ans'>a holder of a 'LP' certificate</span>",
"a licensed gas technician",
"the propane supplier",
"any of these optionse"
]
const Q43A = [
"A bench grinder",
"<span class='ans'>a portable angle grinder</span>",
"a pedestal grinder",
"none of these options"
]
const Q44A = [
"the provincial WHMIS requirements",
"<span class='ans'>the Transport Canada Dangerous Goods regulation</span>",
"the National Energy Board Propane Transportation Act",
"none of these options"
]
const Q45A = [
"<span class='ans'>communication</span>",
"workplace behavior",
"appearance",
"attitude"
]
const Q46A = [
"a comparison between the speed at which items fall and the speed at which a steel ball falls",
"<span class='ans'>a comparison between the weight of a volume of gas (liquid) and equal volume of air (water)</span>",
"a comparison between the gravity at sea levels and the gravity at the installation elevation",
"none of these options"
]
const Q47A = [
"<span class='ans'>when the propane piping through the furnace base consists of a single piece</span>",
"when the piping is schedule 50 steel",
"when the propane is equal parts liquid and vapour",
"when an in-line safety valve is used at least 15 feet from the the main supply line, downstream from the destination"
]
const Q48A = [
"<span class='ans'>A</span>",
"B",
"C",
"D"
]
const Q49A = [
"ASTM",
"ASME",
"NFPA",
"<span class='ans'>CSA</span>"
]
const Q50A = [
"their picture will be located on the official website",
"all inspectors wear white hardhats the say inspector",
"their business card will identify their job function as inspector",
"<span class='ans'>by examining their identification badge or card</span>"
]
const Q51A = [
"The air required to operate the blower fan.",
"The air needed for the draft regulator.",
"<span class='ans'>The air required for satisfactory combustion of a gas.</span>",
"The air required for complete furnace operation."
]
const Q52A = [
"Material safety disconnect switch",
"Mandatory safety data sheet",
"<span class='ans'>Material safety data sheet</span>",
"Material safety display sheet"
]
const Q53A = [
"Hard hat, gloves, glasses",
"Glasses, boots, respiratory",
"Respiratory, gloves, hard hat",
"<span class='ans'>All the above</span>"
]
const Q54A = [
"0.4% to 0.14%",
"10% to 1%",
"3% to 15%",
"<span class='ans'>4% to 15%</span>"
]
const Q55A = [
"1020 F",
"1000 F",
"<span class='ans'>1300 F</span>",
"900 F"
]
const Q56A = [
"1000 F",
"2025 F",
"<span class='ans'>3600 F</span>",
"4500 F"
]
const Q57A = [
"<span class='ans'>25 to 1</span>",
"0.5 to 1",
"10 to 25",
"1 to 1"
]
const Q58A = [
"600 to 1",
"<span class='ans'>270 to 1</span>",
"10 to 1",
"1 to 600"
]
const Q59A = [
"2025 BTU",
"1200 BTU",
"3500 BTU",
"<span class='ans'>1000 BTU</span>"
]
const Q60A = [
"CGA",
"TSSA",
"CSA",
"<span class='ans'>ULC</span>"
]
const Q61A = [
"the third prong is a spare",
"the third prong is a guide to ensure the correct polarity",
"the third prong is a backup power feed to ensure performance",
"<span class='ans'>the third prong is a ground for protection in case of short circuit</span>"
]
const Q62A = [
"<span class='ans'>Seek assistance, and leave if necessary</span>",
"warn them that you are trained in self defense",
"ignore the behavior",
"make jokes to remove the tension from the situation"
]
const Q63A = [
"<span class='ans'>dry</span>",
"wet",
"sweet",
"sour"
]
const Q64A = [
"yes",
"no",
"<span class='ans'>only when permitted by the Act, Regulations or bulletins</span>",
"only when permitted by the manufacturer maintenance instructions"
]
const Q65A = [
"when the tool has 'no grounding required' identification symbol",
"<span class='ans'>when the tool is designated 'double insulated'</span>",
"when the tool is equipped with a removable ground plug",
"when you are not using the tool in wet locations"
]
const Q66A = [
"heat, fuel, CO2",
"heat, fuel CO",
"heat, heat, O3",
"<span class='ans'>heat, fuel, O2</span>"
]
const Q67A = [
"0.25 inch w.c.",
"<span class='ans'>0.5 inch w.c.</span>",
"1.0 inch w.c",
"3.5 inch w.c."
]
const Q68A = [
"<span class='ans'>it is effective in the proper identification of the problem</span>",
"it is effective in demonstrating your knowledge and grasp of the subject",
"it is effective in keeping a record in case of a lawsuit",
"none of these options"
]
const Q69A = [
"the risk of damaging the objects on the customer's driveway is eliminated",
"oil or other fluid spills will not damage the customers driveway",
"children will be less likely to enter or damage your vehicle",
"<span class='ans'>all of these options</span>"
]
const Q70A = [
"google",
"CSA product listing records",
"provincial products registration records",
"<span class='ans'>the manufacturers service bulletins</span>"
]
const Q71A = [
"a file",
"a hacksaw",
"a crimping tool",
"<span class='ans'>pipe dies</span>"
]
const Q72A = [
"flow chart",
"line chart",
"<span class='ans'>pie chart</span>",
"bar chart"
]
const Q73A = [
"contact CSA who will provide a certification specialist to conduct the approval",
"obtain a copy of the B149.3 code for field approvals and follow the instructions contained therein",
"contact the local gas inspector, who will approve the equipment as part of the installation permit.",
"<span class='ans'>approval procedures are identified in the local act, regulations and bulletins</span>"
]
const Q74A = [
"It will void the warranty if it doesn't match",
"the incorrect RPM can overload the grinder",
"<span class='ans'>the wheel could shatter if the RPM rating is incorrect</span>",
"the incorrect RPM can cause a whistle sound that can damage hearing"
]
const Q75A = [
"repeat word like 'I understand' and 'really?' to show you are listening",
"<span class='ans'>restate the explanation to the customer to ensure it has been properly understood</span>",
"tell the customer that it will not be a problem as you have seen much worse",
"ask the customer about sports to get their mind off of their problems"
]
const Q76A = [
"10",
"<span class='ans'>11</span>",
"12",
"14"
]
const Q77A = [
"<span class='ans'>270 - 1</span>",
"470 - 1",
"600 - 1",
"800 - 1"
]
const Q78A = [
"anyone who has verified the appliance is in safe working order",
"any inspector or CSA staff member",
"only members of the Canadian Gas Association",
"<span class='ans'>a certificate holder may remove the notice if he/she is satisfied that corrective action has been taken.</span>"
]
const Q79A = [
"<span class='ans'>National Coarse Thread and National Fine Thread</span>",
"National Finished Thread and National Coated Thread",
"American Street Thread and American Residential Thread",
"Canadian Course Thread and Canadian Treated Thread"
]
const Q80A = [
"lumens",
"<span class='ans'>electrons</span>",
"pretrons",
"positrons"
]
const Q81A = [
"<span class='ans'>flow chart</span>",
"line chart",
"pie chart",
"bar chart"
]
const Q82A = [
"<span class='ans'>propane</span>",
"butane",
"natural gas",
"none of these options"
]
const Q83A = [
"<span class='ans'>you assure the customer that you will not forget why you are there</span>",
"you will have valuable information to include in the final report",
"you are indicating to the customer that you value their input",
"you can create a checklist to ensure the problem is resolved when you have completed your work"
]
const Q84A = [
"rules 16-802 to 16-808",
"rules 10-200 to 10-202",
"rules 26-602 to 26-610",
"<span class='ans'>rules 26-802 to 26-808</span>"
]
const Q85A = [
"yes, if the transfer is conducted at a licensed facility with certified equipment",
"<span class='ans'>yes, if the transfer is conducted by a trained person holding a certificate recognized by the authority having jurisdiction</span>",
"yes, if the transfer is conducted in a pit to contain any leakage",
"no"
]
const Q86A = [
"to check the temperature of operation",
"to check for the composition of the gasses being exhausted",
"<span class='ans'>to check for the safety and efficiency of operation</span>",
"to confirm emission regulation compliance"
]
const Q87A = [
"You will receive a false reading",
"<span class='ans'>the resulting current could damage the meter</span>",
"the resulting current could drain the battery",
"the leads will become permanent magnets"
]
const Q88A = [
"18 inches",
"24 inches",
"36 inches",
"<span class='ans'>48 inches</span>"
]
const Q89A = [
"<span class='ans'>another certificate holder</span>",
"anyone",
"anyone over the age of 19",
"no one"
]
const Q90A = [
"when it has the same number of electrons and neutrons",
"when it has the same number of neutrons and protons",
"<span class='ans'>when it has the same number of electrons and protons</span>",
"when it has the same number of neutrons, protons and electrons"
]
const Q91A = [
"<span class='ans'>this will vary from province to province</span>",
"general construction requirements are not contained in the regulation",
"general construction requirements are contained in Part One",
"none of these options"
]
const Q92A = [
"anyone with a key",
"anyone with permission from the owner",
"<span class='ans'>the person who installed the lock</span>",
"no one"
]
const Q93A = [
"light bulbs in contact with fine dust or oily surfaces",
"broken electrical wiring",
"unshielded switches in dusty areas",
"<span class='ans'>all of these options</span>"
]
const Q94A = [
"<span class='ans'>nitrogen</span>",
"line gas",
"carbon monoxide",
"natural gas"
]
const Q95A = [
"for graphical presentation of information",
"for graphical analysis",
"for computing or determining values",
"<span class='ans'>all of these options</span>"
]
const Q96A = [
"an energy source",
"a conductor",
"a load",
"<span class='ans'>all of these options</span>"
]
const Q97A = [
"the local CSA representative",
"the worker",
"the authority having jurisdiction",
"<span class='ans'>the employer</span>"
]
const Q98A = [
"you fully understand the problem and are competent to correct it",
"<span class='ans'>that you are far too skilled for such a low level task</span>",
"they are fortunate to have someone with your advanced skills looking after their problems",
"none of these options"
]
const Q99A = [
"in the residential occupancies as defined by the national building code",
"<span class='ans'>in industrial occupancies as defined by the national building code</span>",
"in financial occupancies as defined by the national building code",
"all of these options"
]
const Q100A = [
"the gas code",
"the building code",
"<span class='ans'>the electrical code</span>",
"the fire code"
]
const Q101A = [
"920",
"1240",
"<span class='ans'>1300</span>",
"1600"
]
const Q102A = [
"<span class='ans'>nitrogen</span>",
"hydrogen",
"methane",
"air"
]
const Q103A = [
"-2158 C",
"25 F",
"<span class='ans'>-260 F</span>",
"285 F"
]
const Q104A = [
"<span class='ans'>Yes</span>",
"No",
"Only on installed outdoor",
"Only installed indoor"
]
const Q105A = [
"10 to 15",
"20 to 25",
"25 to 35",
"<span class='ans'>20 to 30</span>"
]
const Q106A = [
"<span class='ans'>Step down transformers</span>",
"Step up transformers",
"Auto transformers",
"Neutral transformers"
]
const Q107A = [
"<span class='ans'>Class 1</span>",
"Class 2",
"Class 3",
"All above"
]
const Q108A = [
"12 inches",
"24 inches",
"6 inches",
"<span class='ans'>1 inch</span>"
]
const Q109A = [
"Clock input",
"Leak test",
"<span class='ans'>Consumption of gas</span>",
"Dial accuracy"
]
const Q110A = [
"Yes",
"<span class='ans'>No</span>",
"Yes only if tubing is 1/2 inches or less",
"Yes only if a shut off valve is install"
]
const Q111A = [
"<span class='ans'>2ft</span>",
"3ft",
"4ft",
"6ft"
]
const Q112A = [
"Low voltage",
"High amps",
"<span class='ans'>Broken wire</span>",
"High limit open"
]
const Q113A = [
"0 ppm of CO",
"10 ppm of CO",
"25 ppm of CO",
"<span class='ans'>35 ppm of CO</span>"
]
const Q114A = [
"43 sq ft",
"100 sq ft",
"2400 sq ft",
"<span class='ans'>300 sq ft</span>"
]
const Q115A = [
"Gas well",
"<span class='ans'>Compressor station</span>",
"City gate",
"Pipeline distribution gates"
]
const Q116A = [
"Gas distributor",
"TSSA",
"The B149. -05 code book",
"<span class='ans'>The installer</span>"
]
const Q117A = [
"An updraft condition is present",
"There is excessive draft in the venting",
"<span class='ans'>The venting system of the appliance is restricted or block</span>",
"Low gas pressure to the appliance pilot valve"
]
const Q118A = [
"Short out gas valve",
"<span class='ans'>Short out heat anticipator</span>",
"Short cycle main burner",
"None of these options"
]
const Q119A = [
"10 ft",
"10.5 ft",
"12.5 ft",
"<span class='ans'>12 ft</span>"
]
const Q120A = [
"30 inches",
"<span class='ans'>36 inches</span>",
"38 inches",
"24 inches"
]
const Q121A = [
"600 to 1",
"<span class='ans'>270 to 1</span>",
"10 to 1",
"1 to 600"
]
const Q122A = [
"Ontario Code Regulation Permits",
"T.S.A. Certification Gas Codes",
"C.S.A. Regulation and Certification",
"<span class='ans'>Technical Standards and Safety Authority</span>"
]
const Q123A = [
"<span class='ans'>1.9% to 8.5%</span>",
"2.5% to 5.5%",
"12% to 74%",
"23.5% to 10%"
]
const Q124A = [
"carbon dioxide, nitrogen, soot, heat",
"heat, water, hydrogen, oxygen",
"water, carbon dioxide, oxygen, dioxide",
"<span class='ans'>carbon dioxide, water, nitrogen</span>"
]
const Q125A = [
"fuel, carbon dioxide, air",
"<span class='ans'>heat, oxygen, fuel</span>",
"fuel, air, hydrogen",
"Ignition, propane, nitrogen"
]
const Q126A = [
"Primary air, mixing air, free air",
"<span class='ans'>Combustion air, excess air, dilution air</span>",
"Secondary air, primary air, natural air",
"Venting air, oxygen, excess air"
]
const Q127A = [
"152",
"0.6",
"<span class='ans'>1.52</span>",
"0.06"
]
const Q128A = [
"20% nitrogen 8% oxygen",
"<span class='ans'>80% nitrogen 20% oxygen</span>",
"80% oxygen 20% nitrogen",
"80% hydrocarbon 20% excess air"
]
const Q129A = [
"Carbon dioxide, water, soot, heat",
"<span class='ans'>Carbon monoxide, water, aldehydes</span>",
"Soot, hydrogen peroxide, carbon monoxide, heat",
"aldehydes, carbon trioxide, soot"
]
const Q130A = [
"Excess air",
"<span class='ans'>Primary air</span>",
"Combustion air",
"Dilution air"
]
const Q131A = [
"Venting air",
"Post secondary air",
"<span class='ans'>Secondary air</span>",
"Outside air"
]
const Q132A = [
"<span class='ans'>Air to cool hot flue gases</span>",
"Air to needed for excess air",
"Air to start combustion",
"Air to ensure flame"
]
const Q133A = [
"two",
"three",
"ABC",
"<span class='ans'>four</span>"
]
const Q134A = [
"<span class='ans'>This decision is up to the individual province to decide</span>",
"6",
"12",
"4"
]
const Q135A = [
"36 inches",
"24 inches",
"<span class='ans'>18 inches</span>",
"12 inches"
]
const Q136A = [
"to be listened to",
"to be treated with respect",
"to have their problem taken seriously",
"<span class='ans'>all of the these options</span>"
]
const Q137A = [
"indirect vent",
"B vent",
"<span class='ans'>direct vent type</span>",
"none of these options"
]
const Q138A = [
"blow dryer and curling irons",
"television and stereo equipment",
"microwave",
"<span class='ans'>refrigerators or freezers</span>"
]
const Q139A = [
"95 percent",
"<span class='ans'>80 percent</span>",
"75 percent",
".80 percent"
]
const Q140A = [
"22.30",
"20.50",
"<span class='ans'>16.6</span>",
"18.46"
]
const Q141A = [
"110.00 volts",
"115.25 volts",
"122.60 volts",
"<span class='ans'>125.35 volts</span>"
]
const Q142A = [
"1.42",
"<span class='ans'>4.2</span>",
"41.51",
"15.14"
]
const Q143A = [
"<span class='ans'>25 to 1</span>",
"0.5 to 1",
"1 to 25",
"20 to 1"
]
const Q144A = [
"250 Psig",
"275 Psig",
"350 Psig",
"<span class='ans'>375 Psig</span>"
]
const Q145A = [
"365 psig",
"<span class='ans'>275 psig</span>",
"370 psig",
"375 psig"
]
const Q146A = [
".10",
"<span class='ans'>0.5</span>",
"0.05",
"0.10"
]
const Q147A = [
"CCH4",
"C4H",
"CH3",
"<span class='ans'>CH4</span>"
]
const Q148A = [
"0-30v",
"<span class='ans'>0-250v</span>",
"0-600v",
"0-1000v"
]
const Q149A = [
"Black",
"Gold",
"<span class='ans'>Silver</span>",
"Green"
]
const Q150A = [
"ABD",
"BCD",
"CBA",
"<span class='ans'>ABC</span>"
]
const Q151A = [
"340",
"<span class='ans'>750</span>",
"850",
"1000"
]
const Q152A = [
"Amp meter",
"<span class='ans'>Ohm meter</span>",
"Volt meter",
"Potentiometer"
]
const Q153A = [
"<span class='ans'>Electro-magnetic current</span>",
"D.C. rectifier",
"Transformer",
"Transducer"
]
const Q154A = [
"<span class='ans'>Hydrostatically</span>",
"After being covered",
"With air pressure and a soap solution",
"With air pressure and a fluorescent dye"
]
const Q155A = [
"Black",
"<span class='ans'>Gold</span>",
"Silver",
"Green"
]
const Q156A = [
"Roll out switch",
"<span class='ans'>Safety control</span>",
"Fan control",
"Different switch"
]
const Q157A = [
"Step down transformers",
"<span class='ans'>Step up transformers</span>",
"Auto transformer",
"Neutral transformers"
]
const Q158A = [
"0.34",
"<span class='ans'>3.41</span>",
"3,416",
"34,120"
]
const Q159A = [
"In the duct near the furnace room",
"In the basement near the furnace",
"<span class='ans'>In the living room or hallway</span>",
"In the front entrance"
]
const Q160A = [
"<span class='ans'>A measure of the quantity of electron flow.</span>",
"A measure of the amount of electrical pressure.",
"A measure of how much a circuit will limit current flow.",
"A measure of the amount of power used by a circuit."
]
const Q161A = [
"The quantity of electrons flowing",
"The amount of electrical pressure",
"How much a circuit will limit current flow",
"<span class='ans'>The amount of power used by a circuit</span>"
]
const Q162A = [
"Power decrease",
"<span class='ans'>Voltage increase</span>",
"Resistance decrease",
"Amperage stays consistent"
]




var displayQuestions = false

function compile() {
  massShuffle()
  displayQuestions = true;
  let theQuestions = [
    {
      question: "What is the specific gravity of natural gas vapour?",
      answers: {
        [Q1A[0]]: "",
        [Q1A[1]]: "",
        [Q1A[2]]: "",
        [Q1A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>0.55</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "When lifting in general, which of the following instructions is correct?",
      answers: {
        [Q2A[0]]: "",
        [Q2A[1]]: "",
        [Q2A[2]]: "",
        [Q2A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>the back should be straight and knees bent, to use your leg muscles</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What type of diagram(s) identify only connections, functions and flow? (component location or size and shape are not indicated.)",
      answers: {
        [Q3A[0]]: "",
        [Q3A[1]]: "",
        [Q3A[2]]: "",
        [Q3A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>schematic diagram</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Who does TSSA report to?",
      answers: {
        [Q4A[0]]: "",
        [Q4A[1]]: "",
        [Q4A[2]]: "",
        [Q4A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>The Ontario Ministry of Consumer Services</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What must a Certificate Holder do when it appears that there has been a CO poisoning incident?",
      answers: {
        [Q5A[0]]: "",
        [Q5A[1]]: "",
        [Q5A[2]]: "",
        [Q5A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>immediately shut off the supply of gas to the appliance or work; promptly give oral notice of the shutting off of the gas to the distributor; promptly give written notice to the user, (i) describing the condition that constitutes the immediate hazard, and (ii) directing that the appliance or work not be used until the condition is corrected</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "When dealing with customers, what would a neat, well groomed appearance indicate? ",
      answers: {
        [Q6A[0]]: "",
        [Q6A[1]]: "",
        [Q6A[2]]: "",
        [Q6A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>that your work will reflect the same care and consideration</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What are responsibilities of a gas technician if he or she finds a natural gas or propane appliance that is considered to be an immediate hazard?",
      answers: {
        [Q7A[0]]: "",
        [Q7A[1]]: "",
        [Q7A[2]]: "",
        [Q7A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>responsibilities are identified in the local act, regulations and bulletins</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "When should a CGI never be operated or used?",
      answers: {
        [Q8A[0]]: "",
        [Q8A[1]]: "",
        [Q8A[2]]: "",
        [Q8A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>all of these options</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "How is area expressed in meters? ",
      answers: {
        [Q9A[0]]: "",
        [Q9A[1]]: "",
        [Q9A[2]]: "",
        [Q9A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>m 2 (meters squared)</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What do thin, equally spaced. broken lines indicate on a technical drawing? ",
      answers: {
        [Q10A[0]]: "",
        [Q10A[1]]: "",
        [Q10A[2]]: "",
        [Q10A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>hidden lines</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What would be a good practice after a customer's problem has been solved and the work is complete? ",
      answers: {
        [Q11A[0]]: "",
        [Q11A[1]]: "",
        [Q11A[2]]: "",
        [Q11A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>to perform a follow-up to ensue the customer is still satisfied</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the specific gravity of liquid propane?",
      answers: {
        [Q12A[0]]: "",
        [Q12A[1]]: "",
        [Q12A[2]]: "",
        [Q12A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>0.51</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Identify a local requirement with which NVG refueling stations must comply:",
      answers: {
        [Q13A[0]]: "",
        [Q13A[1]]: "",
        [Q13A[2]]: "",
        [Q13A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>all of these options</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is/are non-verbal technique that can calm the upset customer?",
      answers: {
        [Q14A[0]]: "",
        [Q14A[1]]: "",
        [Q14A[2]]: "",
        [Q14A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>a calm sincere concern and interest in facial expressions</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "When responding to a customers complaint, which is the best wording to use?",
      answers: {
        [Q15A[0]]: "",
        [Q15A[1]]: "",
        [Q15A[2]]: "",
        [Q15A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>I can understand why you feel that way</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Which type of pipe threading die head does not have to be reversed after the thread has been cut?",
      answers: {
        [Q16A[0]]: "",
        [Q16A[1]]: "",
        [Q16A[2]]: "",
        [Q16A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>a quick opening die</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is a type of analyzer?",
      answers: {
        [Q17A[0]]: "",
        [Q17A[1]]: "",
        [Q17A[2]]: "",
        [Q17A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>the tube type and the liquid type</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What Code deals with propane storage and handling currently accepted into law in Ontario?",
      answers: {
        [Q18A[0]]: "",
        [Q18A[1]]: "",
        [Q18A[2]]: "",
        [Q18A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>CSA B149.2-10</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the best alternative communication when a customer's english is heavy accented?",
      answers: {
        [Q19A[0]]: "",
        [Q19A[1]]: "",
        [Q19A[2]]: "",
        [Q19A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>ask the customer to write their request</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the best policy for arguing with customers? ",
      answers: {
        [Q20A[0]]: "",
        [Q20A[1]]: "",
        [Q20A[2]]: "",
        [Q20A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>always avoid conflict and arguments with customers</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the minimum recommended distance to place a new fastener, from a failed fastener, using a power actuated tool? ",
      answers: {
        [Q21A[0]]: "",
        [Q21A[1]]: "",
        [Q21A[2]]: "",
        [Q21A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>3 inches</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the definition of Due Diligence? ",
      answers: {
        [Q22A[0]]: "",
        [Q22A[1]]: "",
        [Q22A[2]]: "",
        [Q22A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>actions that are reasonable in the circumstances and would be conducted by any reasonable person</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the organization that publishes tables of symbols found on piping drawing?",
      answers: {
        [Q23A[0]]: "",
        [Q23A[1]]: "",
        [Q23A[2]]: "",
        [Q23A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>all of these options</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What diameter must a test gauge be?",
      answers: {
        [Q24A[0]]: "",
        [Q24A[1]]: "",
        [Q24A[2]]: "",
        [Q24A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>a minimum 3 inch diameter</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "How can combustible gases be ventilated, provided it is safe to do so?",
      answers: {
        [Q25A[0]]: "",
        [Q25A[1]]: "",
        [Q25A[2]]: "",
        [Q25A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>open doors and windows</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "An appliance rating plate specifies a minimum clearance of 36 inches. What clearance can be used from the sides and rear if a 1/4 inch insulating billboard is installed and spaced 1 inch from the combustible material?",
      answers: {
        [Q26A[0]]: "",
        [Q26A[1]]: "",
        [Q26A[2]]: "",
        [Q26A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>18 inches</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Which type of personal protection should be used when working with chisels?",
      answers: {
        [Q27A[0]]: "",
        [Q27A[1]]: "",
        [Q27A[2]]: "",
        [Q27A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>eye protection</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Name the Ontario Act that directly related to safety and standards within the fuels industry?",
      answers: {
        [Q28A[0]]: "",
        [Q28A[1]]: "",
        [Q28A[2]]: "",
        [Q28A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>the Technical Standards and Safety Act</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Identify the correct blade to be used in a chop saw when cutting non-ferrous metals and plastic? ",
      answers: {
        [Q29A[0]]: "",
        [Q29A[1]]: "",
        [Q29A[2]]: "",
        [Q29A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>a carbide-tipped blade</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the regulatory authority that oversees the safety of both natural gas and propane?",
      answers: {
        [Q30A[0]]: "",
        [Q30A[1]]: "",
        [Q30A[2]]: "",
        [Q30A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>CSA</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "If an employee noticed a contravention of the safety act or regulation, or a job site hazard, who would the employee first report these situations to?",
      answers: {
        [Q31A[0]]: "",
        [Q31A[1]]: "",
        [Q31A[2]]: "",
        [Q31A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>employer or supervisor</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What would accompany the blueprint for a large construction project? (#15-34) (What would accompany the blueprint for a large construction project? ",
      answers: {
        [Q32A[0]]: "",
        [Q32A[1]]: "",
        [Q32A[2]]: "",
        [Q32A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>specifications</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Which type of pipe cutter is best for cutting pipe where there is limited space for rotation?",
      answers: {
        [Q33A[0]]: "",
        [Q33A[1]]: "",
        [Q33A[2]]: "",
        [Q33A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>three wheel cutter</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is a good response to a customer who is demanding unreasonable or impossible performance? ",
      answers: {
        [Q34A[0]]: "",
        [Q34A[1]]: "",
        [Q34A[2]]: "",
        [Q34A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>calmly and patiently identify what you are able to do and not what you are unable to do</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "A beam clamp is an example of ___________ type of fastener. ",
      answers: {
        [Q35A[0]]: "",
        [Q35A[1]]: "",
        [Q35A[2]]: "",
        [Q35A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>pipe</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "When planning an appliance installation, where would you locate the height and space requirements?",
      answers: {
        [Q36A[0]]: "",
        [Q36A[1]]: "",
        [Q36A[2]]: "",
        [Q36A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>the manufacturers product specifications</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "When the scale on a drawing is identified as 1:100, how much larger will the object be compared to the drawing?",
      answers: {
        [Q37A[0]]: "",
        [Q37A[1]]: "",
        [Q37A[2]]: "",
        [Q37A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>100 X</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Propane-burning appliances installed in a mobile home must comply with which standards?",
      answers: {
        [Q38A[0]]: "",
        [Q38A[1]]: "",
        [Q38A[2]]: "",
        [Q38A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Clause 11 of the B149.2-10and the CSA Z240.1</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Eating or smoking on the customer's property is an example of poor: ",
      answers: {
        [Q39A[0]]: "",
        [Q39A[1]]: "",
        [Q39A[2]]: "",
        [Q39A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>workplace behavior</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Where in your province's Occupational Health and Safety Act are the duties of employers and other persons described? ",
      answers: {
        [Q40A[0]]: "",
        [Q40A[1]]: "",
        [Q40A[2]]: "",
        [Q40A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>this will vary from province to province</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What color code is type K copper pipe? ",
      answers: {
        [Q41A[0]]: "",
        [Q41A[1]]: "",
        [Q41A[2]]: "",
        [Q41A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>green</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Who is authorized to work on liquid propane systems? ",
      answers: {
        [Q42A[0]]: "",
        [Q42A[1]]: "",
        [Q42A[2]]: "",
        [Q42A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>a holder of a 'LP' certificate</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Which type of grinder is commonly used to grain bevels and clean weld spatters of pipes? ",
      answers: {
        [Q43A[0]]: "",
        [Q43A[1]]: "",
        [Q43A[2]]: "",
        [Q43A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>a portable angle grinder</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Propane that is offered for transport must comply with which regulations? ",
      answers: {
        [Q44A[0]]: "",
        [Q44A[1]]: "",
        [Q44A[2]]: "",
        [Q44A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>the Transport Canada Dangerous Goods regulation</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Establishing eye contact when speaking and taking notes demonstrates good:",
      answers: {
        [Q45A[0]]: "",
        [Q45A[1]]: "",
        [Q45A[2]]: "",
        [Q45A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>communication</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Which best defines the term specific gravity: ",
      answers: {
        [Q46A[0]]: "",
        [Q46A[1]]: "",
        [Q46A[2]]: "",
        [Q46A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>a comparison between the weight of a volume of gas (liquid) and equal volume of air (water)</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "When can a propane line supplying a furnace in a mobile home or recreational vehicle be routed through a combustion or fresh air make-up opening in the furnace base? ",
      answers: {
        [Q47A[0]]: "",
        [Q47A[1]]: "",
        [Q47A[2]]: "",
        [Q47A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>when the propane piping through the furnace base consists of a single piece</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What type of fire would a water-based fire fire extinguisher be used to fight? ",
      answers: {
        [Q48A[0]]: "",
        [Q48A[1]]: "",
        [Q48A[2]]: "",
        [Q48A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>A</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Who publishes the B149 code handbook? ",
      answers: {
        [Q49A[0]]: "",
        [Q49A[1]]: "",
        [Q49A[2]]: "",
        [Q49A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>CSA</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "How can one recognize an inspector? ",
      answers: {
        [Q50A[0]]: "",
        [Q50A[1]]: "",
        [Q50A[2]]: "",
        [Q50A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>by examining their identification badge or card</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is combustion air? ",
      answers: {
        [Q51A[0]]: "",
        [Q51A[1]]: "",
        [Q51A[2]]: "",
        [Q51A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>The air required for satisfactory combustion of a gas.</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What does MSDS stand for? ",
      answers: {
        [Q52A[0]]: "",
        [Q52A[1]]: "",
        [Q52A[2]]: "",
        [Q52A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Material safety data sheet</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "For self protection you would need? ",
      answers: {
        [Q53A[0]]: "",
        [Q53A[1]]: "",
        [Q53A[2]]: "",
        [Q53A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>All the above</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the explosion limit of natural gas? ",
      answers: {
        [Q54A[0]]: "",
        [Q54A[1]]: "",
        [Q54A[2]]: "",
        [Q54A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>4% to 15%</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the ignition temperature of natural gas? ",
      answers: {
        [Q55A[0]]: "",
        [Q55A[1]]: "",
        [Q55A[2]]: "",
        [Q55A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>1300 F</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the flame temperature of natural gas? ",
      answers: {
        [Q56A[0]]: "",
        [Q56A[1]]: "",
        [Q56A[2]]: "",
        [Q56A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>3600 F</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the air to gas ratio for propane? ",
      answers: {
        [Q57A[0]]: "",
        [Q57A[1]]: "",
        [Q57A[2]]: "",
        [Q57A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>25 to 1</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the expansion rate of propane? ",
      answers: {
        [Q58A[0]]: "",
        [Q58A[1]]: "",
        [Q58A[2]]: "",
        [Q58A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>270 to 1</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the heating value of natural gas per ft cubed? ",
      answers: {
        [Q59A[0]]: "",
        [Q59A[1]]: "",
        [Q59A[2]]: "",
        [Q59A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>1000 BTU</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is the testing agency that certifies venting? ",
      answers: {
        [Q60A[0]]: "",
        [Q60A[1]]: "",
        [Q60A[2]]: "",
        [Q60A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>ULC</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Why are electric power tools equipped with three-prong electrical plugs",
      answers: {
        [Q61A[0]]: "",
        [Q61A[1]]: "",
        [Q61A[2]]: "",
        [Q61A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>the third prong is a ground for protection in case of short circuit</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the best thing to do if a customer becomes unruly or threatening? ",
      answers: {
        [Q62A[0]]: "",
        [Q62A[1]]: "",
        [Q62A[2]]: "",
        [Q62A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Seek assistance, and leave if necessary</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "When heavier hydrocarbons are removed from natural gas. It is then referred to as _______ gas.",
      answers: {
        [Q63A[0]]: "",
        [Q63A[1]]: "",
        [Q63A[2]]: "",
        [Q63A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>dry</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Is the gas technician/fitter permitted to replace electrical components that are directly related to the operation of the gas appliance? ",
      answers: {
        [Q64A[0]]: "",
        [Q64A[1]]: "",
        [Q64A[2]]: "",
        [Q64A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>only when permitted by the Act, Regulations or bulletins</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "In which situation would an electrical power tool not require grounding plug? ",
      answers: {
        [Q65A[0]]: "",
        [Q65A[1]]: "",
        [Q65A[2]]: "",
        [Q65A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>when the tool is designated 'double insulated'</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What are the components of the fire triangle? ",
      answers: {
        [Q66A[0]]: "",
        [Q66A[1]]: "",
        [Q66A[2]]: "",
        [Q66A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>heat, fuel, O2</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "The maximum pressure drop permitted on a natural gas piping system with a supply pressure less than 7 inches w.c. is: ",
      answers: {
        [Q67A[0]]: "",
        [Q67A[1]]: "",
        [Q67A[2]]: "",
        [Q67A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>0.5 inch w.c.</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Why is asking the right questions in the right way important when dealing with customer concerns? ",
      answers: {
        [Q68A[0]]: "",
        [Q68A[1]]: "",
        [Q68A[2]]: "",
        [Q68A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>it is effective in the proper identification of the problem</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Why should park your service vehicle on the street? ",
      answers: {
        [Q69A[0]]: "",
        [Q69A[1]]: "",
        [Q69A[2]]: "",
        [Q69A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>all of these options</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Where would a service technician locate information on a specific appliances service problems? ",
      answers: {
        [Q70A[0]]: "",
        [Q70A[1]]: "",
        [Q70A[2]]: "",
        [Q70A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>the manufacturers service bulletins</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What tool is used to cut external threads on pipe? ",
      answers: {
        [Q71A[0]]: "",
        [Q71A[1]]: "",
        [Q71A[2]]: "",
        [Q71A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>pipe dies</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What type of chart compares individual parts in relation to their total as a sector of a circular area? ",
      answers: {
        [Q72A[0]]: "",
        [Q72A[1]]: "",
        [Q72A[2]]: "",
        [Q72A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>pie chart</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Identify the procedure to obtain a field approval of an appliance requiring testing and inspection: ",
      answers: {
        [Q73A[0]]: "",
        [Q73A[1]]: "",
        [Q73A[2]]: "",
        [Q73A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>approval procedures are identified in the local act, regulations and bulletins</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Identify the procedure to obtain a field approval of an appliance requiring testing and inspection: ",
      answers: {
        [Q74A[0]]: "",
        [Q74A[1]]: "",
        [Q74A[2]]: "",
        [Q74A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>the wheel could shatter if the RPM rating is incorrect</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "After listening to a customer's explanation of the problem, what should you always do? ",
      answers: {
        [Q75A[0]]: "",
        [Q75A[1]]: "",
        [Q75A[2]]: "",
        [Q75A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>restate the explanation to the customer to ensure it has been properly understood</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the speed of a propane flame in inches per second? ",
      answers: {
        [Q76A[0]]: "",
        [Q76A[1]]: "",
        [Q76A[2]]: "",
        [Q76A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>11</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "The expansion ratio of propane from a liquid to a gas at atmospheric pressure is: ",
      answers: {
        [Q77A[0]]: "",
        [Q77A[1]]: "",
        [Q77A[2]]: "",
        [Q77A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>270 - 1</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Who can remove a 'DO NOT USE' notice that has been affixed to an appliance? ",
      answers: {
        [Q78A[0]]: "",
        [Q78A[1]]: "",
        [Q78A[2]]: "",
        [Q78A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>a certificate holder may remove the notice if he/she is satisfied that corrective action has been taken.</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What are the two common thread patterns found on bolts used by the gas technician? ",
      answers: {
        [Q79A[0]]: "",
        [Q79A[1]]: "",
        [Q79A[2]]: "",
        [Q79A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>National Coarse Thread and National Fine Thread</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Atoms are made of particles including: ",
      answers: {
        [Q80A[0]]: "",
        [Q80A[1]]: "",
        [Q80A[2]]: "",
        [Q80A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>electrons</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is a schematic representation of process also know as? ",
      answers: {
        [Q81A[0]]: "",
        [Q81A[1]]: "",
        [Q81A[2]]: "",
        [Q81A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>flow chart</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "A gas with an ignition temperature of 920 F and the chemical designation of C3H8 is commonly referred to as?",
      answers: {
        [Q82A[0]]: "",
        [Q82A[1]]: "",
        [Q82A[2]]: "",
        [Q82A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>propane</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "How will taking notes when the customer is explaining the problem help? ",
      answers: {
        [Q83A[0]]: "",
        [Q83A[1]]: "",
        [Q83A[2]]: "",
        [Q83A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>you assure the customer that you will not forget why you are there</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Which Canadian Electrical Code Rules apply to circuits supplying power to heating equipment that uses solid, liquid or gaseous fuels? ",
      answers: {
        [Q84A[0]]: "",
        [Q84A[1]]: "",
        [Q84A[2]]: "",
        [Q84A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>rules 26-802 to 26-808</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Can propane be transferred from one container to another? ",
      answers: {
        [Q85A[0]]: "",
        [Q85A[1]]: "",
        [Q85A[2]]: "",
        [Q85A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>yes, if the transfer is conducted by a trained person holding a certificate recognized by the authority having jurisdiction</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the purpose of flue gas analysis? ",
      answers: {
        [Q86A[0]]: "",
        [Q86A[1]]: "",
        [Q86A[2]]: "",
        [Q86A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>to check for the safety and efficiency of operation</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Why must an ohmmeter never be connected into a live circuit? ",
      answers: {
        [Q87A[0]]: "",
        [Q87A[1]]: "",
        [Q87A[2]]: "",
        [Q87A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>the resulting current could damage the meter</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the minimum clearance between the front of a swimming pool heater and a combustible material? ",
      answers: {
        [Q88A[0]]: "",
        [Q88A[1]]: "",
        [Q88A[2]]: "",
        [Q88A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>48 inches</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Who can service gas equipment, if under the direct supervision of a certificate holder? ",
      answers: {
        [Q89A[0]]: "",
        [Q89A[1]]: "",
        [Q89A[2]]: "",
        [Q89A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>another certificate holder</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "When is an object considered to be electrically neutral? ",
      answers: {
        [Q90A[0]]: "",
        [Q90A[1]]: "",
        [Q90A[2]]: "",
        [Q90A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>when it has the same number of electrons and protons</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Where can the regulations covering general construction be found? ",
      answers: {
        [Q91A[0]]: "",
        [Q91A[1]]: "",
        [Q91A[2]]: "",
        [Q91A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>this will vary from province to province</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Assuming there is no emergency, who may remove a lock used to lock-out equipment? ",
      answers: {
        [Q92A[0]]: "",
        [Q92A[1]]: "",
        [Q92A[2]]: "",
        [Q92A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>the person who installed the lock</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following electrical sources could cause a fire in the workplace? ",
      answers: {
        [Q93A[0]]: "",
        [Q93A[1]]: "",
        [Q93A[2]]: "",
        [Q93A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>all of these options</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which gas can be used to purge air out of systems with pipe 4 inch and larger? ",
      answers: {
        [Q94A[0]]: "",
        [Q94A[1]]: "",
        [Q94A[2]]: "",
        [Q94A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>nitrogen</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What best identifies the way in which graphs and charts are intended to be used? ",
      answers: {
        [Q95A[0]]: "",
        [Q95A[1]]: "",
        [Q95A[2]]: "",
        [Q95A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>all of these options</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which element is required to form an electrical circuit? ",
      answers: {
        [Q96A[0]]: "",
        [Q96A[1]]: "",
        [Q96A[2]]: "",
        [Q96A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>all of these options</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Who must provide workers with equipment and training that are required by law? ",
      answers: {
        [Q97A[0]]: "",
        [Q97A[1]]: "",
        [Q97A[2]]: "",
        [Q97A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>the employer</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What will displaying arrogant body language demonstrate to the customer? ",
      answers: {
        [Q98A[0]]: "",
        [Q98A[1]]: "",
        [Q98A[2]]: "",
        [Q98A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>that you are far too skilled for such a low level task</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Where may natural gas compressors be installed? ",
      answers: {
        [Q99A[0]]: "",
        [Q99A[1]]: "",
        [Q99A[2]]: "",
        [Q99A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>in industrial occupancies as defined by the national building code</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Which code contains the requirements governing electrical circuits for gas-fired equipment?",
      answers: {
        [Q100A[0]]: "",
        [Q100A[1]]: "",
        [Q100A[2]]: "",
        [Q100A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>the electrical code</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the ignition temperature of natural gas measured in degrees Fahrenheit? ",
      answers: {
        [Q101A[0]]: "",
        [Q101A[1]]: "",
        [Q101A[2]]: "",
        [Q101A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>1300</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is an inert gas? ",
      answers: {
        [Q102A[0]]: "",
        [Q102A[1]]: "",
        [Q102A[2]]: "",
        [Q102A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>nitrogen</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the boiling point of natural gas? ",
      answers: {
        [Q103A[0]]: "",
        [Q103A[1]]: "",
        [Q103A[2]]: "",
        [Q103A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>-260 F</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Can a G3 certificate holder, under direct supervision, install gas piping to a 450 cfh boiler?",
      answers: {
        [Q104A[0]]: "",
        [Q104A[1]]: "",
        [Q104A[2]]: "",
        [Q104A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Yes</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the millivolt open test output of a thermocouple? ",
      answers: {
        [Q105A[0]]: "",
        [Q105A[1]]: "",
        [Q105A[2]]: "",
        [Q105A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>20 to 30</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What are transformers which produce a secondary voltage that is lower than the primary called? ",
      answers: {
        [Q106A[0]]: "",
        [Q106A[1]]: "",
        [Q106A[2]]: "",
        [Q106A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Step down transformers</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "What type of flashlight is needed by code to search for a gas leak? ",
      answers: {
        [Q107A[0]]: "",
        [Q107A[1]]: "",
        [Q107A[2]]: "",
        [Q107A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Class 1</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "For a central furnace what would be the minimum clearance from combustible on the sides?",
      answers: {
        [Q108A[0]]: "",
        [Q108A[1]]: "",
        [Q108A[2]]: "",
        [Q108A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>1 inch</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "The primary use of a gas meter is? ",
      answers: {
        [Q109A[0]]: "",
        [Q109A[1]]: "",
        [Q109A[2]]: "",
        [Q109A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Consumption of gas</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Can a compression fitting be used on copper tubing? ",
      answers: {
        [Q110A[0]]: "",
        [Q110A[1]]: "",
        [Q110A[2]]: "",
        [Q110A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>No</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "A vent passing though a roof line with a zero pitch should extend by? ",
      answers: {
        [Q111A[0]]: "",
        [Q111A[1]]: "",
        [Q111A[2]]: "",
        [Q111A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>2ft</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "If you read infinity on an analog meter what would this mean? ",
      answers: {
        [Q112A[0]]: "",
        [Q112A[1]]: "",
        [Q112A[2]]: "",
        [Q112A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Broken wire</span>",
    },
    {
      question: "Under OSHA what is the permissible exposure to CO level for 8 hours? ",
      answers: {
        [Q113A[0]]: "",
        [Q113A[1]]: "",
        [Q113A[2]]: "",
        [Q113A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>35 ppm of CO</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What would be the square footage of 20' long x 15' wide x 8' high of a building envelope?",
      answers: {
        [Q114A[0]]: "",
        [Q114A[1]]: "",
        [Q114A[2]]: "",
        [Q114A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>300 sq ft</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Mercaptan is usually added to natural gas, where?",
      answers: {
        [Q115A[0]]: "",
        [Q115A[1]]: "",
        [Q115A[2]]: "",
        [Q115A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Compressor station</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Who is responsible for the proper installation of the gas piping to the appliance?",
      answers: {
        [Q116A[0]]: "",
        [Q116A[1]]: "",
        [Q116A[2]]: "",
        [Q116A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>The installer</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Spillage of flue gases at the appliance draft diverter would indicate that:",
      answers: {
        [Q117A[0]]: "",
        [Q117A[1]]: "",
        [Q117A[2]]: "",
        [Q117A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>The venting system of the appliance is restricted or block</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "If the heat anticipator of a thermostat is set to low what probable condition would exist when the heating unit is operating? ",
      answers: {
        [Q118A[0]]: "",
        [Q118A[1]]: "",
        [Q118A[2]]: "",
        [Q118A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Short out heat anticipator</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "How far should the base of a ladder be, from the building, if the ladder is 36 feet high?",
      answers: {
        [Q119A[0]]: "",
        [Q119A[1]]: "",
        [Q119A[2]]: "",
        [Q119A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>12 ft</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "A ladder must extend above roof landing by?",
      answers: {
        [Q120A[0]]: "",
        [Q120A[1]]: "",
        [Q120A[2]]: "",
        [Q120A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>36 inches</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the expansion rate of propane? ",
      answers: {
        [Q121A[0]]: "",
        [Q121A[1]]: "",
        [Q121A[2]]: "",
        [Q121A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>270 to 1</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Who issues gas technician certificates in Ontario? ",
      answers: {
        [Q122A[0]]: "",
        [Q122A[1]]: "",
        [Q122A[2]]: "",
        [Q122A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Technical Standards and Safety Authority</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the flammability range of Butane? ",
      answers: {
        [Q123A[0]]: "",
        [Q123A[1]]: "",
        [Q123A[2]]: "",
        [Q123A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>1.9% to 8.5%</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What are the products of complete combustion?",
      answers: {
        [Q124A[0]]: "",
        [Q124A[1]]: "",
        [Q124A[2]]: "",
        [Q124A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>carbon dioxide, water, nitrogen</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is needed to start combustion? ",
      answers: {
        [Q125A[0]]: "",
        [Q125A[1]]: "",
        [Q125A[2]]: "",
        [Q125A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>heat, oxygen, fuel</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the air needed to operate a gas appliance safely? ",
      answers: {
        [Q126A[0]]: "",
        [Q126A[1]]: "",
        [Q126A[2]]: "",
        [Q126A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Combustion air, excess air, dilution air</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the relative density of propane gas? ",
      answers: {
        [Q127A[0]]: "",
        [Q127A[1]]: "",
        [Q127A[2]]: "",
        [Q127A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>1.52</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is air comprised of? ",
      answers: {
        [Q128A[0]]: "",
        [Q128A[1]]: "",
        [Q128A[2]]: "",
        [Q128A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>80% nitrogen 20% oxygen</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What are the products of incomplete combustion? ",
      answers: {
        [Q129A[0]]: "",
        [Q129A[1]]: "",
        [Q129A[2]]: "",
        [Q129A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Carbon monoxide, water, aldehydes</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What type of air is premixed with gas prior to ignition? ",
      answers: {
        [Q130A[0]]: "",
        [Q130A[1]]: "",
        [Q130A[2]]: "",
        [Q130A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Primary air</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What type of air surrounds the flame for combustion? ",
      answers: {
        [Q131A[0]]: "",
        [Q131A[1]]: "",
        [Q131A[2]]: "",
        [Q131A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Secondary air</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Dilution air is:",
      answers: {
        [Q132A[0]]: "",
        [Q132A[1]]: "",
        [Q132A[2]]: "",
        [Q132A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Air to cool hot flue gases</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "How many symbols or classes of fire extinguishers exist? ",
      answers: {
        [Q133A[0]]: "",
        [Q133A[1]]: "",
        [Q133A[2]]: "",
        [Q133A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>four</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "How many parts are each province's occupational health and safety act divided into? ",
      answers: {
        [Q134A[0]]: "",
        [Q134A[1]]: "",
        [Q134A[2]]: "",
        [Q134A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>This decision is up to the individual province to decide</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the minimum clearance between the front, back and sides of a commercial clothes dryer and a combustible material?",
      answers: {
        [Q135A[0]]: "",
        [Q135A[1]]: "",
        [Q135A[2]]: "",
        [Q135A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>18 inches</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "When a customer is upset they typically want: ",
      answers: {
        [Q136A[0]]: "",
        [Q136A[1]]: "",
        [Q136A[2]]: "",
        [Q136A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>all of the these options</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What type of room heater is permitted to be installed in the bathroom? ",
      answers: {
        [Q137A[0]]: "",
        [Q137A[1]]: "",
        [Q137A[2]]: "",
        [Q137A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>direct vent type</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the best example of an appliance that should never be unplugged in order to obtain electrical power? ",
      answers: {
        [Q138A[0]]: "",
        [Q138A[1]]: "",
        [Q138A[2]]: "",
        [Q138A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>refrigerators or freezers</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the maximum filling density of propane containers? ",
      answers: {
        [Q139A[0]]: "",
        [Q139A[1]]: "",
        [Q139A[2]]: "",
        [Q139A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>80 percent</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "At 100 volts, what would be the amperage in a parallel circuit with a 10 ohm and a 12 ohm resistance?",
      answers: {
        [Q140A[0]]: "",
        [Q140A[1]]: "",
        [Q140A[2]]: "",
        [Q140A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>16.6</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What would be the voltage in a parallel circuit with a 10 ohm and a 12 ohm resistance, whose current is 23 amps?",
      answers: {
        [Q141A[0]]: "",
        [Q141A[1]]: "",
        [Q141A[2]]: "",
        [Q141A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>125.35 volts</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the weight of one gallon of propane? ",
      answers: {
        [Q142A[0]]: "",
        [Q142A[1]]: "",
        [Q142A[2]]: "",
        [Q142A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>4.2</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the air to gas ratio for propane? ",
      answers: {
        [Q143A[0]]: "",
        [Q143A[1]]: "",
        [Q143A[2]]: "",
        [Q143A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>25 to 1</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the relief pressure of a propane tank? ",
      answers: {
        [Q144A[0]]: "",
        [Q144A[1]]: "",
        [Q144A[2]]: "",
        [Q144A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>375 Psig</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the relief pressure set at on a propane cylinder? ",
      answers: {
        [Q145A[0]]: "",
        [Q145A[1]]: "",
        [Q145A[2]]: "",
        [Q145A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>275 psig</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "If you had 60 watts light bulb at 120 volts what would be the amperage? ",
      answers: {
        [Q146A[0]]: "",
        [Q146A[1]]: "",
        [Q146A[2]]: "",
        [Q146A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>0.5</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the chemical composition of natural gas? ",
      answers: {
        [Q147A[0]]: "",
        [Q147A[1]]: "",
        [Q147A[2]]: "",
        [Q147A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>CH4</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "When it has been determined that the voltage to a unit is approximately 115 Volts, which range should an analog volt meter be set at?",
      answers: {
        [Q148A[0]]: "",
        [Q148A[1]]: "",
        [Q148A[2]]: "",
        [Q148A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>0-250v</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "On a 120 volt receptacle, the neutral connection terminals are: ",
      answers: {
        [Q149A[0]]: "",
        [Q149A[1]]: "",
        [Q149A[2]]: "",
        [Q149A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Silver</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is the most common fire extinguishers used in the work place? ",
      answers: {
        [Q150A[0]]: "",
        [Q150A[1]]: "",
        [Q150A[2]]: "",
        [Q150A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>ABC</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "One horsepower equals_______ watts. ",
      answers: {
        [Q151A[0]]: "",
        [Q151A[1]]: "",
        [Q151A[2]]: "",
        [Q151A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>750</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which meter is used to check for continuity? ",
      answers: {
        [Q152A[0]]: "",
        [Q152A[1]]: "",
        [Q152A[2]]: "",
        [Q152A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Ohm meter</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "A solenoid valve is activated by a/an: ",
      answers: {
        [Q153A[0]]: "",
        [Q153A[1]]: "",
        [Q153A[2]]: "",
        [Q153A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Electro-magnetic current</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Underground piping shall be tested for leaks: ",
      answers: {
        [Q154A[0]]: "",
        [Q154A[1]]: "",
        [Q154A[2]]: "",
        [Q154A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Hydrostatically</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "On a 120 volt receptacle, the line connection terminals are:",
      answers: {
        [Q155A[0]]: "",
        [Q155A[1]]: "",
        [Q155A[2]]: "",
        [Q155A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Gold</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following best describes a device used to prevent an unsafe? Condition of temperature, pressure, or liquid level? ",
      answers: {
        [Q156A[0]]: "",
        [Q156A[1]]: "",
        [Q156A[2]]: "",
        [Q156A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Safety control</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Transformers which produce a secondary voltage which is higher than the Primary are said to be: ",
      answers: {
        [Q157A[0]]: "",
        [Q157A[1]]: "",
        [Q157A[2]]: "",
        [Q157A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Step up transformers</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "One watt equals ______ Btuh.",
      answers: {
        [Q158A[0]]: "",
        [Q158A[1]]: "",
        [Q158A[2]]: "",
        [Q158A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>3.41</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "Which of the following is the best location for a residential central heating thermostat? ",
      answers: {
        [Q159A[0]]: "",
        [Q159A[1]]: "",
        [Q159A[2]]: "",
        [Q159A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>In the living room or hallway</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "What is current? ",
      answers: {
        [Q160A[0]]: "",
        [Q160A[1]]: "",
        [Q160A[2]]: "",
        [Q160A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>A measure of the quantity of electron flow.</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "A watt is a unit of measure of:",
      answers: {
        [Q161A[0]]: "",
        [Q161A[1]]: "",
        [Q161A[2]]: "",
        [Q161A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>The amount of power used by a circuit</span>"
    },
    {
      question: "If resistance is constant in a resistive circuit when current increases what happens? ",
      answers: {
        [Q162A[0]]: "",
        [Q162A[1]]: "",
        [Q162A[2]]: "",
        [Q162A[3]]: ""
      },
      correctAnswer: "<span class='ans'>Voltage increase</span>"
    }
  ];
  var UserNumOfQuestions = document.getElementById("NumQuestionsInput").value;
  shuffle(theQuestions);
  console.log(theQuestions);
  let myQuestions = theQuestions.slice(0, UserNumOfQuestions);

  function buildQuiz() {
    // we'll need a place to store the HTML output
    const output = [];

    // for each question...
    myQuestions.forEach((currentQuestion, questionNumber) => {
      // we'll want to store the list of answer choices
      const answers = [];

      // and for each available answer...
      for (String in currentQuestion.answers) {
        // ...add an HTML radio button
        answers.push(
          `<label id ="label${questionNumber}">
            <input type="radio" name="question${questionNumber}" value="${String}">
            ${String}
            ${currentQuestion.answers[String]}
          </label>`
        )
      }

      // add this question and its answers to the output
      output.push(
        `<div class="question"> ${currentQuestion.question} </div>
        <div class="answers"> ${answers.join("")} </div>`
      );
    });

    // finally combine our output list into one string of HTML and put it on the page
    quizContainer.innerHTML = ('<ol><li>'+output.join('</li><li>')+'</li></ol>');
  }

  function showResults() {

    // gather answer containers from our quiz
    const answerContainers = quizContainer.querySelectorAll(".answers");
    const questionContainers = quizContainer.querySelectorAll(".question");

    // keep track of user's answers
    let numCorrect = 0;

    // for each question...
    myQuestions.forEach((currentQuestion, questionNumber) => {
      // find selected answer
      const answerContainer = answerContainers[questionNumber];
      const selector = `input[name=question${questionNumber}]:checked`;
      const userAnswer = (answerContainer.querySelector(selector) || {}).value;

      // if answer is correct
      if (userAnswer === currentQuestion.correctAnswer) {
        // add to the number of correct answers
        numCorrect=numCorrect+1;

        // color the answers green
        questionContainers[questionNumber].style.color = "green";;
      } else {
        // if answer is wrong or blank
        // color the answers red
        questionContainers[questionNumber].style.color = "red";
        }
        var elements = document.getElementsByClassName('ans');

        for (var i = 0; i < elements.length; i++) {
          var element = elements[i];
          element.style.color = "black";
          element.style.fontWeight = "600";
      }
    });

    // show number of correct answers out of total
    resultsContainer.innerHTML = `${numCorrect} out of ${myQuestions.length} = ${numCorrect*100/myQuestions.length}%`;
  }

  const quizContainer = document.getElementById("quiz");
  const resultsContainer = document.getElementById("results");
  const submitButton = document.getElementById("submit");

  // display quiz right away
  if (displayQuestions == true) {
    buildQuiz();
   }

  // on submit, show results
  submitButton.addEventListener("click", showResults);

}
massShuffle()
function shuffle(array) {
  var currentIndex = array.length, temporaryValue, randomIndex;

  // While there remain elements to shuffle...
  while (0 !== currentIndex) {

    // Pick a remaining element...
    randomIndex = Math.floor(Math.random() * currentIndex);
    currentIndex -= 1;

    // And swap it with the current element.
    temporaryValue = array[currentIndex];
    array[currentIndex] = array[randomIndex];
    array[randomIndex] = temporaryValue;
  }

  return array;
}

function massShuffle() {
  shuffle(Q1A);
  shuffle(Q2A);
  shuffle(Q3A);
  shuffle(Q4A);
  shuffle(Q5A);
  shuffle(Q6A);
  shuffle(Q7A);
  shuffle(Q8A);
  shuffle(Q9A);
  shuffle(Q10A);
  shuffle(Q11A);
  shuffle(Q12A);
  shuffle(Q13A);
  shuffle(Q14A);
  shuffle(Q15A);
  shuffle(Q16A);
  shuffle(Q17A);
  shuffle(Q18A);
  shuffle(Q19A);
  shuffle(Q20A);
  shuffle(Q21A);
  shuffle(Q22A);
  shuffle(Q23A);
  shuffle(Q24A);
  shuffle(Q25A);
  shuffle(Q26A);
  shuffle(Q27A);
  shuffle(Q28A);
  shuffle(Q29A);
  shuffle(Q30A);
  shuffle(Q31A);
  shuffle(Q32A);
  shuffle(Q33A);
  shuffle(Q34A);
  shuffle(Q35A);
  shuffle(Q36A);
  shuffle(Q37A);
  shuffle(Q38A);
  shuffle(Q39A);
  shuffle(Q40A);
  shuffle(Q41A);
  shuffle(Q42A);
  shuffle(Q43A);
  shuffle(Q44A);
  shuffle(Q45A);
  shuffle(Q46A);
  shuffle(Q47A);
  shuffle(Q48A);
  shuffle(Q49A);
  shuffle(Q50A);
  shuffle(Q51A);
  shuffle(Q52A);
  shuffle(Q53A);
  shuffle(Q54A);
  shuffle(Q55A);
  shuffle(Q56A);
  shuffle(Q57A);
  shuffle(Q58A);
  shuffle(Q59A);
  shuffle(Q60A);
  shuffle(Q61A);
  shuffle(Q62A);
  shuffle(Q63A);
  shuffle(Q64A);
  shuffle(Q65A);
  shuffle(Q66A);
  shuffle(Q67A);
  shuffle(Q68A);
  shuffle(Q69A);
  shuffle(Q70A);
  shuffle(Q71A);
  shuffle(Q72A);
  shuffle(Q73A);
  shuffle(Q74A);
  shuffle(Q75A);
  shuffle(Q76A);
  shuffle(Q77A);
  shuffle(Q78A);
  shuffle(Q79A);
  shuffle(Q80A);
  shuffle(Q81A);
  shuffle(Q82A);
  shuffle(Q83A);
  shuffle(Q84A);
  shuffle(Q85A);
  shuffle(Q86A);
  shuffle(Q87A);
  shuffle(Q88A);
  shuffle(Q89A);
  shuffle(Q90A);
  shuffle(Q91A);
  shuffle(Q92A);
  shuffle(Q93A);
  shuffle(Q94A);
  shuffle(Q95A);
  shuffle(Q96A);
  shuffle(Q97A);
  shuffle(Q98A);
  shuffle(Q99A);
  shuffle(Q100A);
  shuffle(Q101A);
  shuffle(Q102A);
  shuffle(Q103A);
  shuffle(Q104A);
  shuffle(Q105A);
  shuffle(Q106A);
  shuffle(Q107A);
  shuffle(Q108A);
  shuffle(Q109A);
  shuffle(Q110A);
  shuffle(Q111A);
  shuffle(Q112A);
  shuffle(Q113A);
  shuffle(Q114A);
  shuffle(Q115A);
  shuffle(Q116A);
  shuffle(Q117A);
  shuffle(Q118A);
  shuffle(Q119A);
  shuffle(Q121A);
  shuffle(Q122A);
  shuffle(Q123A);
  shuffle(Q124A);
  shuffle(Q125A);
  shuffle(Q126A);
  shuffle(Q127A);
  shuffle(Q128A);
  shuffle(Q129A);
  shuffle(Q130A);
  shuffle(Q131A);
  shuffle(Q132A);
  shuffle(Q133A);
  shuffle(Q134A);
  shuffle(Q135A);
  shuffle(Q136A);
  shuffle(Q137A);
  shuffle(Q138A);
  shuffle(Q139A);
  shuffle(Q140A);
  shuffle(Q141A);
  shuffle(Q142A);
  shuffle(Q143A);
  shuffle(Q144A);
  shuffle(Q145A);
  shuffle(Q146A);
  shuffle(Q147A);
  shuffle(Q148A);
  shuffle(Q149A);
  shuffle(Q150A);
  shuffle(Q151A);
  shuffle(Q152A);
  shuffle(Q153A);
  shuffle(Q154A);
  shuffle(Q155A);
  shuffle(Q156A);
  shuffle(Q157A);
  shuffle(Q158A);
  shuffle(Q159A);
  shuffle(Q160A);
  shuffle(Q161A);
  shuffle(Q162A);
}
